We tell everyone what Abdullah's routine is
basically.  I used to say, leave it
friend, why don't you tell me, what is the need to tell me.
But what happens is that people think that perhaps
you are doing all the work absolutely accurately and
perfectly since the luxury room was built.
Hey boy.
But guys, this luxury room has
deteriorated a bit since it was built.  He has an iPhone.
It goes to 50 places
with us.  He eats and drinks the same thing that we eat, it's not like he is
eating anything different.
Third, whatever work you ask him to do, he no longer does it.
Hey, are you lying?  He is lying.   I used to do
this earlier.  Earlier it was bound by time.  He knew that
I work.
Look, he is also a brother.  Works here too.
But he is not doing his work responsibilities at all.
Meaning a work is done responsibly.
Why are you not doing that brother?  My wife is
fed up.   So will you dance
?
We know how many fish we have removed.  Do you know
?   Yes.
Ever since we came to this house, we have thrown out about four male
cows.
And what did you take out?  Only on vacation.   On
leave.  It's only on holidays that she does
such good work.
Otherwise she did good work.  So we have taken out four
months.  It has been taken out
because look, when you pay someone
and when you give responsibility to someone, then
because of that payment he also
takes responsibility, when he gets money, like
we are getting money from work, then we are working.
I should not say that whatever it is, even if you do
n't pay me, I will still
do the work.  A thought comes to a person's mind that there are some people
who work even without money.   You are doing the
work
when we are also paying you money.   We are
giving you all the luxuries.
You are doing everything.
You are roaming around.  Then why are you not doing the work properly
?
Son, you won't be able to do it.
And how much work do you have?
You just have to turn on the geyser after waking up in the morning.  Ok?   After
waking up in the morning, you just have to open the gate for the nanny.
And I have to go and drop off the stale one and bring it back.
And do you have to take the stale one to leave?  And
what else do you have to do?  There is a vegetable, someone
ordered some stuff from downstairs.  Now there
are online apps.  We order it from him at night.  Please
tell me how much work is there.  Guys, one thing is that there is a
lot of work.  So this
guy might not be doing it.  The work is just two to three.
In which sir also makes TikTok,
also makes vlogs on which he also travels.
Still it is not working.  Hmm